{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "This aboriginal language is ___ difficult one to learn.",
      "a": "quite the",
      "b": "quite a",
      "c": "the quite",
      "d": "a quite",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Quite a something/quite some something: used before a noun to emphasize that something is very good, large, interesting",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Anne is _________ child to speak out.",
      "a": "too a shy",
      "b": "too shy",
      "c": "a too shy",
      "d": "too shy a",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Adj + noun \n+ Too adj (for sbd) to do sth ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm _________ willing to give you a hand.",
      "a": "very",
      "b": "too",
      "c": "enough",
      "d": "so",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Very [+ adjective/adverb]: used to emphasize an adjective, adverb, or phrase",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does that guy with curly hair speak Chinese? \"He speaks Mandarin Chinese ___.\"",
      "a": "excellent",
      "b": "very good",
      "c": "so good",
      "d": "very well",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Adverbs modify verbs, adjectives, and other adverbs \n+ \"Well\" modifies \"speak\" ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mr. Churchill looks _________. But last year he was not in ___.",
      "a": "well, good health",
      "b": "well, well healthy",
      "c": "good, well healthy",
      "d": "good, good health",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n- Verb of appearance: (feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem)+ Adjective : modifies the noun before the verb\n- \"Well\" (adj)= healthy",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That railway extends ___.",
      "a": "to east",
      "b": "the east",
      "c": "in the east",
      "d": "eastward",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Eastward: towards or in the east",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The businessperson knows ___ little English that he can't make himself understood.",
      "a": "such",
      "b": "so",
      "c": "less",
      "d": "much",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ".\n- So+ adj/ adv + that:  used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I saw your keys ___.",
      "a": "anywhere",
      "b": "everywhere",
      "c": "where",
      "d": "somewhere",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Somewhere: in or to a place, but you do not say or know exactly where \n- Anywhere: used in questions to mean 'somewhere', used in negative sentences to mean no place \n- Everywhere: in or to every place \n- Where: use in question sentence ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "My goodness, look at the time! It's eight o'clock ___ and Johnny's ___ at breakfast.",
      "a": "yet, still",
      "b": "already, yet",
      "c": "already, still",
      "d": "still, already",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": ".\n- Already: before now, or before a particular time\n- Still: up to a particular point in time and continuing at that moment\n- Yet: used in negative statements and questions to talk about whether something that was expected has happened",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sea is not ___ calm.",
      "a": "such a",
      "b": "then",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "than",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- That (adv) + adjective/adverb: used to say how big, how much etc, especially when you are showing the size, amount etc with your hands",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "11",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}